{
    "subject": "resource/Clarissa_S._Williams",
    "predicate": "property/predecessor",
    "object": "resource/Emmeline_B._Wells",
    "human_readable": "Clarissa S. Williams was preceded by Emmeline B. Wells.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9659499526023865,
            "question": "Who preceded Clarissa S. Williams?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9586416482925415,
            "question": "Was Emmeline B. Wells succeeded by Clarissa S. Williams?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9037793874740601,
            "question": "If Emmeline B. Wells was a leader, what role might Clarissa S. Williams have had?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8922788500785828,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Emmeline B. Wells and Clarissa S. Williams?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8552180528640747,
            "question": "Can you describe the lineage between Emmeline B. Wells and Clarissa S. Williams?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6830846071243286,
            "question": "Name the person who came before Clarissa S. Williams."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.583624541759491,
            "question": "Who held a position before Clarissa S. Williams?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.03761931508779526,
            "question": "In what order did these two individuals hold their positions?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.02429359219968319,
            "question": "What can we infer about the potential significance of this succession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.02254548668861389,
            "question": "Are there any historical records about the transition of power between these two individuals?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Clarissa S. Williams was preceded by Emmeline B. Wells.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2267_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What can we infer about the potential significance of this succession?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2267_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what order did these two individuals hold their positions?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2267_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who held a position before Clarissa S. Williams?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2267_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2267_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2267_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2267_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2267_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2267_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2267_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2267_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2267_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2267_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2267_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Clarissa S. Williams was preceded by Emmeline B. Wells.\" Specifically, one document states, \"In April 1921, Sister Clarissa\u00c2 S. Williams succeeded Sister Emmeline\u00c2 B. Wells as Relief Society general president,\" which indicates that Wells came before Williams in terms of her position."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}